export let MCQS = [
  {
    question: "HTTP stands for",
    choice1: "Hyper Text Tranport Port",
    choice2: "Hyper Text Transport protocol",
    choice3: "hyper  Text Transfer Protocol",
    choice4: "Hyper Transport Text Protocol",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which class is computer threats?",
    choice1: "Dos Attack",
    choice2: "Phishing",
    choice3: "Soliciting",
    choice4: "Both A and C",
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is unsolicited commercial email",
    choice1: "Virus",
    choice2: "Malware",
    choice3: "Spam",
    choice4: "All of the above",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is used in WiFI hacking",
    choice1: "Aircrack-ng",
    choice2: "Wireshark",
    choice3: "Norton",
    choice4: "All of the above",
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "which port and Ip scanner is common",
    choice1: "Cain and Abel",
    choice2: "Angry IP Scanner",
    choice3: "Snort",
    choice4: "Ettercap",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "In cyber security, there are____types of scanning:",
    choice1: "1",
    choice2: "2",
    choice3: "3",
    choice4: "4",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of scanning",
    choice1: "Xmas Tree Scan",
    choice2: "Cloud scan",
    choice3: "Null Scan",
    choice4: "SYN Stealth",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: " In system hacking, which is the most crucial activity?",
    choice1: "Information gathering",
    choice2: "Covering tracks",
    choice3: "Cracking passwords",
    choice4: "None of the above",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following are the types of scanning?",
    choice1: "Network, vulnerability, and port scanning",
    choice2: "Port, network, and services",
    choice3: "Client, Server, and network",
    choice4: "None of the above",
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is considered as the first computer virus?",
    choice1: "Sasser",
    choice2: "Blaster",
    choice3: "Creeper",
    choice4: "Both A and C",
    answer: 2,
  },
];
